https://www.wildroots.net/privacy.php?osCsid=c84ae9aeff179a4f524f4cc9f84c346a

Cart ContentsCheckoutMy Account
Top » Catalog » Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Stony Mountain Botanicals. Ltd.
does not sell, trade or share your email, phone or address information with
any other company. We occasionally mail to our customer list, but we do
not sell your information to other marketers.
We use your phone number only to be able to contact you in case of problems
with your order.
Our site uses secure encryption technology for the transmission of your order.
Our shopping cart uses uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We don't use cookies for any other purposes.
This site contains links to other sites.
Stony Mountain Botanicals is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
This site makes forums and message boards available to its users.
Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
We do not email you with advertising unless you have signed up for the Stony Mountain Botanicals Newsletter or Sales Flyer.
To be removed from Stony Mountain Botanicals Newsletter
You can send email to orders at wildroots.net
To modify or request removal of your address from our database
email orders at wildroots.net
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the
practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site,
you can contact
orders at wildroots.net
Continue
Categories Apothecary Supplies->Bath & Body->Bulk Herbs & Spices->Essential OilsHydrosol
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Information
Ordering Policies Privacy Notice Terms Contact Us
Shopping Cart 0 items
Bestsellers Eucalyptus Essential OilOrange Essential Oil - SweetTea Tree Essential OilDandelion Leaf C/S OrganicLavender Essential OilRed Raspberry Leaf C/SPsyllium Seed Whole OrganicCinnamon Sticks 2.75" Organic 3%Nettle Leaf C/S OrganicPeppermint Leaf C/S
Specials Echinacea ang. Herb C/S Organic$21.00$10.50
Reviews There are currently no product reviews
Enjoy Our Local Flora
Copyright © 2020 Stony Mountain BotanicalsPowered by osCommerce
